<resources>
    <string name="app_name">W4TW Workshop</string>

    <!-- reading task -->
    <string name="reading_task0_header">Introduction</string>
    <string name="reading_task0_content">The Water for the World Workshop introduces participants to the issues of clean water access and how local economy, geography and literacy are all connected. Using this app, you will try to build a water filter to access clean water for yourself!</string>

    <string name="reading_task1_header">The Workshop</string>
    <string name="reading_task1_content">The Water for the World presentation is an engaging hour and a half that educates, challenges, and inspires students to think about creative solutions to global water access issues. Our program is divided into a three–part learning format as recommended by the Ontario Ministry of Education – Opening (Minds On), Middle (Action – Interactive/Hands–On), Closing (Debrief/Consolidation).\nA large component of the presentation involves hands–on interaction where groups of 4–6 students construct their own water filters using recycled plastic bottles and multiple layers of sand and gravel. The students are grouped into different countries, and are provided with different levels of information and amounts of play money, depending on their country’s literacy rate and wealth, respectively.\nThrough this activity, students are challenged to think critically and creatively, while collaborating with their peers. Students will gain a better understanding of social issues in technological development, while being exposed to the concept of international interdependence and cooperation as it relates to the global need for potable water. We also aim to engage students by highlighting the potential role youth can have in addressing these issues.</string>

    <string name="task4_header">Literacy Rate</string>
    <string name="task4_content">The Literacy rate is a good indication of the general level of education in a country. Explore this map and ask you self – where are the literacy rates the lowest in the world?</string>

    <string name="task12_header">Filter Building Challenge</string>
    <string name="task12_content">Many people in the world drink dirty water and get sick or die. \n
    Your challenge is to build a water filter to turn the glass of water</string>
    <string name="task12_footer">Press NEXT to start the challenge</string>

    <!-- sliding scale task -->
    <string name="tooShort">The answer is too small</string>
    <string name="tooLarge">The answer is too large</string>
    <string name="task2_header">Clean Water Access</string>
    <string name="task2_subtitle">There are approaching 8 billion people in the world. How many of them do you think do not have access to clean drinking water in their home?</string>
    <string name="task2_correctInfo">Yes! around 800 million people - 1 in 10 of the world’s population - don’t have clean drinking water within a 30-minute trip from their home and 1 in 4 (2 billion!) don’t have it in their home</string>

    <string name="task6_header">Q: What is Extreme Poverty ?</string>
    <string name="task6_subtitle">A: Living on less than $2.50 a day\nHow many people do you think live on less than $2.50 a day?</string>
    <string name="task6_correctInfo">Yes! 1 Billion people in the world live in Extreme Poverty – think what you could buy with $2.50 – what could you eat and how would your or your parents be able to pay your rent</string>

    <!-- mc task-->
    <string name="task3_header">Where do most of the people without clean water access live?</string>
    <string name="task3_option0">North America</string>
    <string name="task3_option1">South America</string>
    <string name="task3_option2">Europe</string>
    <string name="task3_option3">Asia</string>
    <string name="task3_option4">Africa</string>
    <string name="task3_popup">Yes, most of the people in the world living without clean water live in Sub-Saharan Africa – the part of Africa south of the Sahara </string>

    <string name="task7_header">Where do most of the people in extreme poverty live?
</string>
    <string name="task7_option0">North America</string>
    <string name="task7_option1">South America</string>
    <string name="task7_option2">Europe</string>
    <string name="task7_option3">Asia</string>
    <string name="task7_option4">Africa</string>
    <string name="task7_popup">Yes, most of the people in the world living in extreme poverty live in Sub-Saharan Africa – the part of Africa south of the Sahara. Click NEXT to see how poverty varies around the world.
</string>

    <!-- short answer task -->
    <string name="task8_question">How did the money and literacy rate you were given for each affect your ability to build a water filter?</string>
    <string name="task9_question">Do you think water and its use around the world is fair and equal? Should people have the same access to water everywhere?</string>
    <string name="task10_question">What can you do in your daily life to conserve water?</string>
    <string name="task11_question">What is the most important thing you have learned doing this activity?</string>

    <string name="instruction_general">1. Loosely put a cotton plug in the neck of the cut bottle, then cover the neck of the bottle with a piece of cheese cloth secured with a rubber band.\n2. Pour a 1-cm layer of fine sand over the cotton plug, followed by 1-cm of coarse sand, fine gravel, and coarse gravel.\n3. Clean the filter by slowly and carefully pouring through 1-litre of clean water (over a bucket).\n4.Place the filter over a plastic cup. Now, test your water filter by pouring half of the dirty water through the filter.</string>

    <!-- GLR task -->
    <string name="task_8_content">Extreme Poverty is defined by the percentage of the population living on less than $2.50 a say. This amp shows where most of those suffering from extreme poverty live:</string>
</resources>